제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주, 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
금요일 밤 9시 37분
Saturday, 9:37 p.m.
에릭의 차 안
Eric Forman's
Vista Cruiser
"은신처"
"The Point"
"Night Moves" by Bob Seger
and the Silver Bullet Band
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
암것도 아냐
Nothing.
그 뒤에 잘 돼가니?
How's it going back there?
도나, 분명히 말하는데
나 브라 풀고 있던 거 아냐
Okay, Donna, just for that,
I'm not taking your bra off.
그래 뭐, 어쨌든 못 풀었으니까
You weren't taking it off anyway.
여보세요, "꼬꼬 하우스"죠?
Hello, House of Chicken?
너 날개가 얼마만 하냐?
How big are your wings?
가슴이라니까
Breasts.
너 가슴이 얼마만 하냐?
How big are your breasts?
전 페즌데, 누구세요?
This is Fez, who is this?
내 첫번째 장난전화였어
My first prank call.
너랑 있으면 매일 저녁이
모험의 연속이라니까
Every night with you is an adventure.
그래, 페즈
롤러 코스터 타는 거 같지?
Yeah, Fez, it's
a real roller coaster, ain't it?
하이드, 근데 넌
왜 여자친구가 없는거야?
Hyde, how come
you do not have a girlfriend?
이 머리를 어떻게 좀 하면
생길지도 몰라
Maybe if you did something
with your hair.
야, 너!
Hey, you, is there
a motel in this pukehole?
이 똥통같은 동네에도
모텔이라는 게 있냐?
똥통을 세개 지나면
"졸릴때 여관"이 나와
There's a Sleepy Time Lodge
three pukeholes over.
고마워
난 크리시야
Thanks. I'm Chrissy.
- 난 하이드
- 누가 물어봤냐?
- I'm Hyde.
- Who cares.
내 뿅카 타고 가서
어딘지 알려줄래?
You wanna hop on my Vespa
and show me where it is?
스쿠터의 대명사 이태리제 베스파
세상에, 나 널 사랑하나 봐
Mother of God, I think I love you.
사랑은 자본가들이 여성을 착취하기
위해 사용하는 구시대적 개념이야
Love is an outdated concept...
used by industrialists
to keep women subservient.
"Anarchy in the U.K."
by The Sex Pistols
이런, 나 정말 널 사랑해
Mother of God, I do love you.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x22 Punk Chick
Jun 21, 1999 on FOX
젠장
Damn.
왜 그러는데?
What happened?
내가 너한테 15:0으로 졌잖아
You just beat me 15-nothing.
그게 뭐?
So what?
막대기로 공을 튀기는 건
너무 지루해
I mean, hitting a ball
with two paddles is so boring.
난 뭔가 획기적인
도전거리가 필요해
I need a new challenge,
something totally different.
공을 치긴 치는데..
I need to hit the ball with...
더 작은 막대기로 하는 거야
smaller paddles.
아저씨 연장 어디 있냐?
Where's Red keep his tools?
아빠 퐁 게임은 안돼
그거 건드리면..
No. Not Red's Pong.
I don't think you should be going...
차고! 맞아!
The garage! Of course!
야, 네가 그거 망가뜨리면
날 야단치실 거란 말야
Okay, if you screw that up,
he's gonna blame me.
나도 알아
I know.
이런 깡촌에서 너처럼 급진적인
동지를 만나게 될 줄 몰랐어
Who'd have thought
I'd meet a radical number like you...
in a slag heap town like this.
나도 널 만난 게 믿기지 않아
I can't believe
you're just passing through, man.
넌 음울하고 밉살맞은 데다
You're dark, you're obnoxious...
위험할 정도로 편집증이야
you're dangerously paranoid.
오늘밤 널 만나기 전엔
너 같은 애가 있는 줄도 몰랐어
Until tonight, I didn't even know
a girl like you existed.
우리가 같이 자게 될 거란
생각도 못해 봤겠네?
Has it occurred to you
that we're on a bed?
야, 이건 너무 완벽해
Man, this is so perfect.
너 헤프기까지 한 거야?
You're easy, too?
응
Yeah.
권력층은 우리가 섹스하는 걸
좋아하지 않아
See, the establishment
doesn't want us having sex...
그걸 하면 우리 기분이
좋아지는 걸 알기 때문이지
because they know
it makes us feel good, right?
우리끼리 알아서 즐거울 수 있다면
자기네가 왜 필요하겠어?
So if we can feel good on our own,
what do we need the establishment for?
그러니까, 우리가 하는 섹스는
So, every time we have sex...
위대한 저항을 의미해
it's a huge protest.
이거 알아?
You know what?
나 위대한 저항감이
밀려오는게 느껴져
I think I feel a huge protest
coming on.
제 가정 숙제 도와주셔서
정말 고마워요, 아줌마
Thank you so much...
for helping with
my home ec project, Mrs. Forman.
천만에
You're welcome, honey.
재키, 파이 만들어 본 적 있니?
Now, Jackie,
have you ever made a pie before?
아뇨, 전 요리는 잘 안해요
나중에 외모로 먹고 살거거든요
No, I don't really cook much.
I just plan on getting by on my looks.
그렇구나
Okay, then.
마이클
Michael.
재키
Jackie.
- 여기서 뭐 하니?
- 파이 굽고 있어
- What are you doing here?
- I'm baking a pie.
난 막대기 작게 만들어
I'm making small paddles.
알았어
Fine.
도나, 우리 오늘밤에
잠깐 드라이브가 갔다 올까?
So, Donna, what say
you and I take a little drive tonight?
글쎄, 너 차문이나 열 수 있겠니?
I don't know.
Do you think you can unlock the car?
우리 셋이 어디로 드라이브 갈까?
Where should the three of us go
on our drive?
페즈, 실은 도나랑 나만 가려고..
Actually, Fez,
just Donna and I are gonna...
알았어
I see.
너희들이 날 따 시킨단 말이지?
So, you are going to ditch me.
하이드처럼
Just like Hyde.
매일 난 진실한 마음으로
여기에 와
Every day, I am here
with my heart on my sleeve...
내가 바라는 건
우정과 포용일 뿐이야
hoping only for friendship
and acceptance.
그런데 내게 남겨진게 뭐지?
And what do I get?
버려짐
Abandonment.
외로움
Loneliness.
이 페즈의 차례는 언제야?
When is it Fez's turn?
내 창녀는 어딨는 거냐구?
Where is my whore?
하이드, 나쁜 자식! 나 빼놓고
혼자 말타다 오는 거야?
Damn you, Hyde. Did you go
horseback riding without me?
아니
No.
크리시라는 정말 멋진 여자애를 만났어
I just met
the most amazing woman. Chrissy.
걘 뉴욕에서 새출발해 보려고
다 버리고 떠나왔대
And she just ditched her entire life
to start over in New York, man.
잠깐, 잠깐
Wait.
- 뉴욕엔 왜 가는데?
- 펑크 밴드를 결성할 거래
- Why is she going to New York?
- She's going to start a punk band.
펑크 밴드라고?
A punk band.
멋지군, 근데 펑크가 뭐야?
Cool. What is punk anyways?
펑크는 조직화된 록큰롤 세력에
대항한 무정부주의자들의 외침이야
Punk is the nihilistic outcry...
against the corporate
rock and roll takeover.
혁명에 바치는 음악이라구
It's the soundtrack
to the revolution, man.
전엔 "블루 오이스터 컬트"의 음악이
혁명에 바치는 음악이라며?
I thought you said Blue Oyster Cult
was the soundtrack to the revolution.
중요한 건 걔가 나한테
같이 떠나자고 했다는 거야
Look, the point is
that she asked me to go with her.
넌 뉴욕엔 왜 가려고 하는데?
Why would you
want to go to New York?
대도시잖아
술집은 새벽 4시까지 영업하고
It's a big city, man,
the bars are open until 4:00...
모든 음악이 탄생하는 곳이야
that's where all the music's
happening.
- 내가 거기 가기만 하면..
- 넌 거기 못가
- If I can make it there...
- You can't make it there.
- 그래도 내가 거기 가기만 하면..
- 그래도 넌 거기 못 간다니까
- But if I can make it there...
- But, you won't make it there.
그냥 좀 들어볼래
Would you just listen.
내가 거기 가기만 하면..
If I can make it there...
젠장, 포먼
너 때문에 뭔지 까먹었잖아!
Damn it, Forman,
now I lost my train of thought!
켈소! 10초 안에
뭐하는 짓인지 말해라
Kelso! You have 10 seconds
to tell me what you're doing.
설명할 수 있어요
I can explain...
- 9초!
- 그게요..
Nine seconds!
See...
- 8초!
- 그래도 셀 것까지는..
Eight!
But the counting...
- 3초!
- 네?
- Three.
- What?
- 5초나 건너뛰시면 어떡해요?
- 이제 됐어. 3초!
- There's no way that was five seconds.
- It is now. Three!
- 전 그냥..
- 2초!
- I just wanted...
- Two.
- 막대기를 줄이려고요
- 시간 됐다!
- Smaller paddles.
- Time!
때리지 마세요!
Don't hurt me!
막대기를 줄인다고?
Smaller paddles?
망가진 거냐?
Is it broken?
전 '퐁 게임'을 너무 잘 해요
Okay, I'm too good at Pong.
이건 저주예요
It's a curse.
무슨 말인지 안다
너무 시시해
I know what you mean.
It's boring.
나도 한달이 넘도록
한번도 안 했어
I haven't played this thing
in over a month.
맞아요. 그렇다니까요
제 말 좀 들어 보세요
Right. Exactly.
Okay, now stay with me here.
그래서 제가 이걸 분해했어요
That's why I took it apart.
See smaller paddles equal bigger fun.
막대기가 짧아지면
더 재밌어질 테니까요
일리가 있어 보이는구나
You may have something there.
어디 한번 해 보자
We'll give it a try.
어차피 분해한 것 같으니 말이다
Seeing as you already opened it.
좋아요
Great.
이거 다시 원래대로 조립 못 하면
나한테 118 달러 내야 된다
And if we can't put it back together,
you owe me $118.
저 118 달러 없는데요
I don't have $118.
그럼 죽으면 되겠구나
Then I'll have to kill you.
괜찮다
Okay.
재키, 괜찮다, 얘야
반성해 보자구나
Jackie, all right, honey.
Let's just review.
네 생각엔 뭐가 잘못된 것 같니?
What do you think
went wrong with this pie?
- 계란이 너무 많아서요?
- 아니
- Too many eggs?
- No.
- 팬이 너무 작아서요?
- 전혀 그렇지 않아
- The pan was too small?
- Not even close.
마이클이 더 이상
절 사랑하지 않아서요?
Is it because Michael doesn't
love me anymore?
비슷하구나
Almost.
네가 이번엔 잘 한다 약속하고선
파이는 안 들여다 보고
It's because you were
talking on the phone about Michael...
전화로 마이클 얘기만
하고 있었으니까 그렇지
instead of watching the pie,
like you promised me you would this time.
또 말이야
Again.
이 거짓말쟁이
You liar.
잘 모르겠다, 하이드
여기서 넌 쿨한 녀석이야
I don't know, Hyde.
I mean, here, you're the cool guy.
그치만 뉴욕에 쿨한 놈들이
얼마나 많이 사는지 알아?
But do you know
how many cool guys live in New York?
예를 들면..
There's like...
'루 리드' 말이야!
'벨벳 언더그라운드'의 리더
Lou Reed, man!
그런데 끼고 싶은 거야?
Do you want to mess with that?
왜 포인트 플레이스를 떠나려고 해?
재밌는데
Why do you want to leave
Point Place? It is fun.
그래, 재밌긴 하지
Yeah, it is fun, man...
게다가 너희들이
정말 그리울 거야
and I'm gonna miss
the hell out of you guys.
그치만 크리스도 멋져
But Chrissy's cool.
게다가 '빅 애플'이잖아
뉴욕의 애칭
And it's the Big Apple, man.
전화번호부에
'루 리드'도 있을까?
Do you think Lou Reed's
in the phone book?
그 사람 분명히 날
좋아할텐데 말야
Because I bet he'd really like me.
루 리드라..
Lou Reed.
어디 가는데?
Where are you going?
크리시는 누구야?
Who's Chrissy?
여기도 나쁘지 않아
TV도 있지..
It's not bad here, man.
We got the TV.
땅콩 버터에..
이것도 있단 말야
And peanut butter.
And I got this thing.
공은 건조기 밑에
들어가 버렸어
The ball part rolled under the dryer.
하이드, 떠나지 마
Hyde, you cannot leave.
니가 나 처음
맥주 먹인 날 기억나?
You gave me my first beer,
remember?
내가 경찰한테 토해 버렸잖아
And then I threw up on that cop.
정말 재밌었지
That was a good time, man.
야, 기다려 봐
Wait a minute, back up...
왜 다들 나만 따 시켜?
nobody tells me anything.
공은 대체 뭐하려고
건조기 밑에 기어 들어간거야?
What's the ball doing
under the dryer?
하이드는 정말
떠날 건가 보구나
So, Hyde's like really leaving.
그래
Yeah.
이건 마치..
It's like...
시간은 자꾸 흘러가 버리는데
time's just passing us by.
그런데, 넌..
무척이나 여유로워 보여
You know, you've got to like...
seize the day.
- 네 말이 맞아
- 그래
- You are so right.
- Yeah.
왜 웃는 거야?
Okay, what's so funny?
아무것도 아냐
Nothing.
아니긴, 말해봐
No, tell me.
네가 브라 풀려는거
금방 알 수 있어
I know you're going for the bra.
어떻게 아는데?
How did you know?
내 브라 풀려고 할 때면
네 입술이 안 움직이거든
It's just, every time you go for my bra,
your lips stop moving.
그래서..
So...
넌 전혀 재미없는 거야?
you're really not having any fun?
아니, 난 즐거워
No, I'm having a good time.
그냥 내 속옷갖고 낑낑대지 말고
집중해줬으면 좋겠어
I would just like a little attention
while you're struggling with my underwear.
나도 여기 있잖아
I'm here too.
맨날 쌍둥이들한테만
신경쓰지 말고
It doesn't always have to be
about the twins.
쌍둥이들?
The twins?
넌 그걸 그렇게 부르는 거야?
Is that what you call them?
그거 정말 야하다
That is so very hot.
알았어
Okay.
집에 갈래
Take me home.
재키
Jackie...
돈 갖고 가서
파이를 사다 내렴
just take the money and buy a pie.
아줌마, 사서 내는 건
부정행위고, 그럼 전 낙제예요
Mrs. Forman, if I buy a pie,
that's cheating and I'll fail.
내말대로 해
어차피 구워서 내도 넌 낙제야
Trust me. If you bake it,
you'll fail, too.
하이드가 뉴욕에 간다는 건 뭐야?
What's this about
Hyde moving to New York?
아뇨. 걘 겨우 17살이에요
걔 엄마가 절대 안 보낼 거예요
No. He's only 17.
His mother would never let him do that.
마이클이 그러는데 하이드 엄마가
술을 많이 마신대요
Actually, Michael told me
that Hyde's mom drinks a lot.
아마 신경도 안 쓰실 걸요?
알콜 중독자들이 어떤지 아시잖아요
She probably won't even care.
You know drunk people are like that.
Okay...
다시 파이를 만들어 보자
let's make another pie.
내가 파이 속을 만드마
I will make the filling...
그리고 내가 껍질도 만드마
and I will make the crust.
전 뭘 만들어요?
What will I make?
넌 거실에 가서
내 술이나 한잔 만들어 오렴
You will go into the living room
and make me a drink.
그 녀석은 고등학교 중퇴하면 안돼
He can't just drop out of high school.
게다가 뉴욕은 17살짜리 꼬마가
지낼만한 곳이 못 되고
And New York City is no place
for a 17-year-old kid.
지하철이 있는 '소돔과 고모라'죠
It's Sodom and Gomorrah
with a subway.
우리가 그 놈이랑
얘길 해야겠어
We'll have to have a talk with him.
그 놈 애미는 절대 안 할게 뻔하니까
His mom sure as hell won't do it.
누군가 그 자식 정신 좀
바짝차리게 해줘야 돼
And somebody's got to beat
some sense into that idiot.
당신 꽤 챙기네요
Red, you do care.
- 가서는 안 된다
- 뉴욕은 위험한 곳이야
- We don't think that you should go.
- New York is a dangerous place.
앞으로는 고등학교 졸업장이 꼭 필요해
A young man today
needs a high school diploma.
뉴욕에선 이유도 없이
사람을 공격한데
In New York, you get mugged
for no good reason.
일자리 구하는 게
어떤 건지 알기나 하냐?
Do you have any idea
what the job market is like?
거기 사람들은 무례해
The people are rude.
넌 마음이 너무 여려
And you have feelings.
대학졸업장이 없으면
넌 아무 것도 아니다
Without that sheepskin,
you are nothing.
네가 지금 아무 것도 아닌 거랑은
또 다른 거다
And not the kind of nothing
that you are now.
더 수준 낮고 더 비참한
아무 것도 아닌 거야
An even lower,
more pathetic nothing.
그 사람들 침도 뱉는단다!
They spit. That's right, they spit!
네 이력서에다 뭐라고 쓸 거냐?
What are you gonna
put on your resume?
"멍청이" ?
"Dumbass"?
전 하나도 안 무서워요!
그러니까 갈 거예요
I'm not afraid of anything,
and I'm going.
뭐 어쨌든 시도는 했으니까
That didn't go that great.
수고했어, 여보
Way to go, Kitty.
야, 건드리지 마!
Hey, don't touch!
내가 이 뭐시기냐를 떼 보겠다
I'm about to take off the doohickey.
잠깐요
Wait.
먼저 이차회로기판에서 트랜지스터의
연결을 끊어놔야 되지 않을까요?
Red, don't you think
we should disconnect...
the transistor from the
secondary circuit board first?
그래
Sure.
그런 다음, 여기 이..
And then, we'll work on the...
뭐시기를 손 보자
doohickey.
좋아요
Bitching.
이건 내 가방이기도 해요!
It is too my suitcase!
이 집 물건 중에 니 껀 없어!
Nothing in this house is yours!
됐어요!
Shut up!
너희 엄마가 이 문제로
화가 많이 나셨나 보구나?
So, your mom's taking it pretty hard?
아니, 아직 얘기 안 했어
No, I haven't told her yet.
하이드, 이렇게 까지 해서
꼭 가야 되겠니?
So, Hyde, you're, like,
really going through with this?
그래
Yeah, man.
거기 사람들이 침도 뱉고
쥐는 사람 머리통만 하다는 것도 알아
I mean, you know.
I know people spit on you there...
and the rats are as big
as your head or whatever.
그치만 내가 여길 벗어날
유일한 기회일지도 몰라, 포먼
But this might be
my only chance to escape, Forman.
넌 지금 떠나면 안돼
You can't leave now.
우린 이제서야 이 동네에
심각한 타격을 줄 수 있을 만큼 컸잖아
We're finally getting old enough
to do some serious damage to this town.
급수탑에 대마초 그리기로
했던 거 기억나?
Remember we were gonna
paint that pot leaf on the water tower?
공공기물 훼손이라, 유혹적이지만..
Vandalism, while tempting...
날 붙잡아 둘 정도는 아니야
is not enough reason for me to stay.
게다가, 나 없이도 할 수 있잖아?
Plus, you can do that without me.
그치만 너 없으면 안 하게 될걸?
But we won't do that without you.
하이드, 우린 네 덕분에 온갖 바보같고
무분별한 짓들을 할 수 있는 거야
Hyde, you're the reason we do
so many stupid, senseless things.
그래, 그건 맞아
Yeah, that is true.
하이드, 이건 너한테만 하는 얘긴데..
Hyde, I've never
told this to another human being...
나..
but I...
도나 브라를 못 풀겠어
Cannot get Donna's bra off.
- 후크야, 스냅이야?
- 둘다. 계속 바꿔 차서 헷갈리게 해
- Hooks or snaps?
- Both. She keeps throwing me changeups.
좋아, 방법을 가르쳐 주지
All right, here's what you do, okay?
브라를 하나 산 다음
그걸로 집에서 연습을 해
You buy a bra
and you practice on it at home...
그런 다음 그걸
도나한테 선물하는 거야
then you give it to Donna as a gift.
거봐, 역시 대단하다니까
See, that's brilliant.
넌 정말 사악한 천재야, 친구!
You're like an evil genius, man!
가방은 어딨니?
Where's your bag?
너 안 가는구나
You're not going.
그래
No.
그치만 네 시간만 괜찮으면
다시 한번 저항을 하고 싶어
But I'd like to mount another protest
if you have the time.
이건 뉴욕 내 친구 전화번호야
This is my friend's
number in New York.
전화 하지 마!
Don't call me.
알았어, 안 할게
Yeah, I won't.
크리시..
Chrissy...
나 여기 수건 훔쳐가도 돼?
do you mind if I steal the towels?
미안해
Sorry.
내가 벌써 챙겼어
I already got them.
켈소, 행운을 빈다
Kelso. Good luck.
네, 정말 힘들었어요, 아저씨
Yeah, she's been
a great ride, man.
- 된다!
- 짧은 막대기예요!
- It worked!
- Smaller paddles!
축하한다, 애야
Congratulations, son.
넌 미래를 내다 봤던 거야
You have seen the future.
맞아요, 아저씨
가정용 컴퓨터, 이게 바로 미래예요!
Yeah. You're so right, Red.
Home computers. That is the future.
아니. 컴퓨터가 아니라
납땜 말이다
No. Not computers. Soldering.
미래는 납땜의 세상이야
The future is soldering.
컴퓨터는 무슨..
Computers.
어떻게 된 거지?
우리 또 주차해 버렸네?
What do you know,
we're parked again.
맞아, 그치만 이번엔
얘기만 할 거야
Right, but this time I just want to talk.
도나, 내가 널 불편하게 했다면
정말 미안해
Donna, I'm really sorry...
if I did anything
to make you feel uncomfortable.
고마워
Thanks.
내 잘못도 있는 거 같아
I guess part of that's my fault.
그치만 네가 좋아할 만한 일이 있어
But I think I know something
that will make you feel better.
좋아
Okay.
있지, 요새 나 좀 힘들었거든
You know,
I've been having a rough time lately.
우리는 사귀는 사이가 되고
알다시피 난 피임약도 먹는데
Now that we're boyfriend and girlfriend
and you know I'm on the pill...
넌 날 주물러 댈려고만
하는 거 같았어
it's like you're always pawing at me.
나도 그런게 좋긴 하지만
내가 널 2루에 보내주면
I wanna fool around,
but then I think if you get to second base...
넌 홈에 들어오고 싶어할 게 뻔하고
you'll get a pretty good view of home.
그렇게 되면 우리 사이는
어떻게 되겠어?
If that happens,
what will happen to you and me?
재키와 켈소가 어떻게 됐는지 봐
Look at what happened
to Jackie and Kelso...
섹스를 하면 모든게 변한단 말야
그것도 아주 짜증나게
and sex changes everything
and that really sucks.
알았어
Okay.
그런데, 그 얘기 중에 어떤 부분에서
내가 좋아했어야 되는 거야?
So, what part of that
was supposed to make me feel better?
나 오늘 노브라야
I'm not wearing a bra.
넌 세상에서 제일 좋은 여자친구야
You are the best girlfriend ever.
내가 안 가서 놀랐냐?
You surprised to see me?
아니, 안간 거 알고 있었어
No, I knew you'd stay.
그래, 넌 나에 대해 너무 많이 알아
Yeah, we've been friends
way too long.
아니, 크리시가 오토바이 뒤에
딴 놈을 태우고 가더라고
No, Chrissy just drove by
with some guy on the back of her bike.
불쌍한 자식
Poor kid.
나땜에 슬퍼서 그런 걸 모르고
She's grieving.
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24